<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>openstack on brk3.github.io</title>
    <link>https://brk3.github.io/categories/openstack/</link>
    <description>Recent content in openstack on brk3.github.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 12:46:12 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://brk3.github.io/categories/openstack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying virtual baremetal with Ironic &amp; Kolla</title>
      <link>https://brk3.github.io/post/kolla-ironic-libvirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 12:46:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brk3.github.io/post/kolla-ironic-libvirt/</guid>
      <description>A common barrier to entry when looking to try out OpenStack Ironic is that you need a baremetal machine to use with it. It turns out that it is possible to use a virtual machine in lieu of baremetal, and this is exactly what tools such as devstack and tripleo allow for. This guide details how the same setup can be done using Kolla. Given the complexity of Ironic and the variety of configurations possible, almost every step will have a multitude of variations and possibilities, I just detail what worked for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debugging Murano with Kolla</title>
      <link>https://brk3.github.io/post/debugging-murano-with-kolla/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 16:31:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brk3.github.io/post/debugging-murano-with-kolla/</guid>
      <description>The kolla-ansible project recently gained support for hacking on the OpenStack services it deploys, much the same as devstack.
Services are being added as we go, so it&amp;rsquo;s unlikely all will be supported for the Pike release. That said it&amp;rsquo;s quite easy to add support for new projects, so if the one you&amp;rsquo;re interested in isn&amp;rsquo;t there yet have a go!
I&amp;rsquo;ve been using this for the past month or so to submit patches into the Murano project, and wanted to give a short overview of how Kolla can be used to do this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nested Xen</title>
      <link>https://brk3.github.io/post/nested-hvm-xen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 16:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brk3.github.io/post/nested-hvm-xen/</guid>
      <description>As part of efforts to more regularly test the Xen hypervisor with Nova as part of OpenStack development, I&amp;rsquo;m spending some time figuring out how to virtualise Xen on Xen, specifically Oracle&amp;rsquo;s Oracle VM Server.
In virtualisation terms the different levels of hypervisor are referred to as LN, where N is the nesting level. In our setup, Oracle VM Server 3.4.2 (OVM-S) is running on baremetal as L0, another instance of OVM-S is running on that as L1, and the final OpenStack instantiated guest would be L2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>